Guide to the Time Inc. Life Publishing and Business Records 1936-2001 MS 3009-RG 26
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Business Office Files, 1937-2001; 10.97 Linear feet in 15 record cartons
  - Subseries II.B. Business Manager Office Files, 1969-1979; 0.35 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    Winston Cox worked in the Comptroller's Office from 1969 to 1971. From 1969 to 1970, he was administration assistant but was promoted to director of budgets and financial analysis in 1970. In 1972, Cox moved to Life and became business manager. He remained in this position until 1974 when he became general manager of Business Development.
    George Dowling worked as business manager at Life from 1969 to 1970. It is unclear what position he held between 1970 and 1972 at which point he left Time Inc.
    Bob Cowin was Sports Illustrated circulation manager from 1964 to 1966. At this time, the title was changed to circulation director and he continued in this position until 1969. In 1970, Cowin became administrative assistant for circulation within the Corporate group. He remained in this position until 1972 when he joined Life as assistant publisher, a positiom he remained in until 1974 when he left Time Inc.
    Mary Davis served as Life business manager from 1978 to 1982 at which time she became general manager. She remained in this position until 1987 when she joined the Magazine Publishing group and became vice president of magazine manufacturing services.
    Priscilla Ricciardi can only be found in the department heads list in 1974 when she served as assistant business manager in Magazine development.
    The Business Manager Office files covers the period of 1969 to 1979 and includes materials from a variety of Life Business Department staff. The names that appear most often are Winston Cox, George Dowling, Bob Cowin, Mary Davis, and Priscilla Riccardi. Included in this series are reports on the average circulation of magazines, notes, budget reports, sales analysis reports, reports on newsstand revenue, clippings, ad rate cards, press releases, lists of Life staff, and correspondence. The correspondence in this subseries discusses circulation statistics, subscription rates, budgets, and ad sales and revenue.
    - Dowling, George: Budget Preparation, 1969-1970 (Offsite-box 3023, Folder 20)
    - Life Special Operating Statements, 1978-1979 (Offsite-box 3023, Folder 21-22)
    - Life Specials: 1977, 1974-1977 (Offsite-box 3023, Folder 23)
    - Old Life: 1972/1973, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 1-2)
  - Subseries II.C. Business Manager Agreement and Licensing Files, 1971-2000; 1.4 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    The Business Manager Agreement and Licensing files cover the period of 1971 to 2000 and focuses on agreements concerning joint projects between Life and outside organizations as well as on licensing agreements. These licensing agreements usually concerned the use or reprinting of an image or photographs either by Life or another organization. Included in this subseries are Life sales reports, contracts, notes on sales report, clippings, reports on costs of production, cd roms, contact lists, lists of back issue dealers, photographs, promotional materials, lists of photographer and rights, tax forms, trademark guidelines, lists of agreements, and correspondence. The correspondences discusses the Life century book, purchase orders, permission for the use of photographs, photographer policy statements, and reprinting pictures.
    - Axel Springer Verlag AG [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Back Issues, 2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 3)
    - Best Friends, undated (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 4)
    - Bugs Bunny [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Cats of Africa [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Circle Fine Art [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Contracts, 2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 5)
    - Contracts: Century Book, undated (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 6)
    - Contracts: Century Book [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Contracts: Century Book: Fall 1999, 1999-2000, undated (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 7)
    - Contracts: Century Book: Fall 1999 [RESTRICTED], 1998-1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Cover Photo Credits, undated (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 8)
    - Cover Policy, 1990 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 9)
    - Faces of Life CD Rom, 1997 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 10)
    - The Face of Life CD Rom [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Offsite-box R27)
      Contained within this folder is a sealed copy of the The Face of Life: A Collection of Life Magazine Covers and Classic Images: 1936 through 1972.
    - Fifty Years of Life [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Freedom Forum [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Graphique de France [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R27)
    - Graves, Michael [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Holson Burnes [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Homestyles [RESTRICTED], 1998 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Jacobsen, Hugh [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - The Joy of Life, 1989 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 11)
    - The Joy of Life [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Kellog [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Kennedy, John F. [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Kodak, 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 12)
    - Kodak [RESTRICTED], 1999-200 (Offsite-box R27)
      Included with the restricted materials are two cd roms. One cd rom has a note written on it which says: "Life Decades Canada 3-15-00". The other cd rom appears to be a sample cd which was sent to Life by Kodak and includes examples of the images that would appear in the time capsule for the millennium.
    - Kodak: Canada [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Kodak: USA/Canada: 1999 Agreement (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 13)
    - Kodak: USA/Canada: 1999 Agreement [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life at Camelot [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Book 2: How We Changed America in Pict, 2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 14)
    - Life Book 2: How We Changed America in Pict [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Engagement Cal [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Faces, 1991 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 15)
    - Life Faces [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life in WWII, 1989 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 16)
    - Life in WWII [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Laughs Last [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Looks Back [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Miscellany [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life: The Sixties [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Life Smiles Back [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R27)
    - LPS: Doris O'Neil Agreement, 1993 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 17)
    - LPS: Doris O'Neil Agreement [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Offsite-box R27)
    - The Marketing Partnership [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Offsite-box R27)
    - MCI [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Offsite-box R27)
    - The Meaning of Life, 1991 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 18)
    - The Meaning of Life [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R27)
    - MILK PEP (Processor Education Program) [RESTRICTED], 1997-1998 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Millennium Monument, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 19)
    - MOMS [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Monroe, Marilyn [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Mulfinger [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - One Hundred Classic Photos, 1987 (Offsite-box R27)
    - O'Neil, Doris Contract [RESTRICTED], 1992-1993 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Our Century in Pictures for Young People, 2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 20)
    - Permissions, 1996-2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 21-24)
    - Permissions [RESTRICTED], 1998-2000 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Permissions: Vince Gill, 2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 25)
    - Permissions: Gill, Vince [RESTRICTED], 2000 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Photographers: Policy Statements on Payments, 1971, 1981-1990, 1996-1999 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 26)
    - Power, J.D., 1999 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 27)
    - Power, J.D. [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Press Net International, 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 28)
    - Press Net International [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - QDE [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Offsite-box R27)
    - R and R [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Ralston [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Sales Graphic [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Schindler, Aaron D. [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Shurman [RESTRICTED], 1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Sixty TV: Photo License, 1996 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 29)
    - Sixty TV: Photo License [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Offsite-box R27)
    - State Farm [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Offsite-box R27)
    - State Farm: General, 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 30)
    - State Farm: General [RESTRICTED], 1996 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Stern [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Sulkes, Kathy, undated (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 31)
    - Sulkes, Kathy [RESTRICTED], 1992-1993 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Taliesin, 1996-2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 32)
    - Taliesin [RESTRICTED], 1996-1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Trademark Guidelines, 2000 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 33)
    - Turner Network TV [RESTRICTED], 1993 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Wedlick, Dennis [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Wild Wolf [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Offsite-box R27)
    - Zeko, Dean, 1996-1999 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 34)
    - Zeko, Dean [RESTRICTED], 1998-2000 (Offsite-box R27)
    - ZM Productions, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box R27)
    - ZMC (Zaloom, Michenaud, and Cowan): Rocket Science, 1998 (Offsite-box R27)
  - Subseries II.D. Financial Statements, 1937-1973; 5.625 Linear feet in 6 record cartons, 1 flat box
    The Financial Statement subseries covers the period of 1937 to 1970. Included in this series are financial statements, budget reports, budget forecasts, budget estimates, mechanical budgets, and operating statements. While the materials are grouped together, it is unclear which office they originated from since there are a variety of names listed on the documents. Some items indicate that the reports were for the business office but do not indicate a specific office of origin or owner.
    Arranged alphabetically with retained binder covers at the end.
    - General Ledger, 1972 (Offsite-box 3040, Folder 6)
    - Life Budget: 1971 (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 35)
    - Life Budget: 1971: Production and Distribution (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 36)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1950 Final Budget: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 37)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1951 First Budget: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 38)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1952 Final Budget: Circulation (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 39)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1953 Final Budget: Circulation Promotion (Offsite-box 3024, Folder 40)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1954 Final Budget: Circulation Department (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 1)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1955 Final Budget: Circulation Department (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 2)
    - Life Budgets: 1950-1956: 1956 Final Budget: Circulation Department (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 3)
    - Life Budgets: 1957-1962: 1957 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 4)
    - Life Budgets: 1957-1962: 1958 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 5)
    - Life Budgets: 1957-1962: 1959 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 6)
    - Life Budgets: 1957-1962: 1960 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 7)
    - Life Budgets: 1957-1962: 1961 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 8)
    - Life Budgets: 1957-1962: 1962 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 9)
    - Life Budgets: 1963-1967: 1963 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 10)
    - Life Budgets: 1963-1967:1964 Mechanical Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 11)
    - Life Budgets: 1963-1967: 1965 Budget: Mechanical (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 12)
    - Life Budgets: 1963-1967: 1966 Mechanical Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 13)
    - Life Budgets: 1963-1967: 1967 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 14)
    - Life Budgets: 1968-1970: 1968 Mechanical Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 15)
    - Life Budgets: 1968-1970: 1969 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 16)
    - Life Budgets: 1968-1970: 1970 Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 17)
    - Life Budgets: 1968-1970: 1970 Mechanical Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 18)
    - Life Budgets: 1968-1970: 1970 Original Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 19)
    - Life Circulation Department: 1972 Original Budget (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 20)
    - Life International: International Magazines Budget: George J. Dowling, 1967 (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 21-22)
    - Life International: Original Budget, 1968 (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 23)
    - Life International: 1970 Second Half (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 24)
    - Life Statements, 1937 (Offsite-box 3025, Folder 25)
    - Life Statements, 1937-1945 (Offsite-box 3026, Folder 1-12)
    - Life Statements, 1956-1966 (Offsite-box 3026, Folder 13-20)
    - Life Statements, 1966-1971 (Offsite-box 3027, Folder 1-19)
    - Life Statements, 1971-1972 (Offsite-box 3028, Folder 1-10)
    - Mechanical Budget, 1972 (Offsite-box 3028, Folder 11)
    - Operating Statements, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3028, Folder 12-15)
    - Original Budget: 2nd Half 1970: Mechanical (Offsite-box 3028, Folder 16-17)
    - Status Report on the Disposition on the Life, 1973 (Offsite-box 3028, Folder 18)
    - Weekly Report: Week Ending 1972 December 23 (Offsite-box 3028, Folder 19)
    - Financial statements binder covers, 1937-1941 (Offsite-box 3029)
  - Subseries II.E. General Files, 1980-1999; 0.34 Linear feet in 3 folders
    The General Files includes financial material about Life removed from two binders.
    - Audit Bureau of Circulations (ABC): Magazine Publisher's Statements, 1980-1999 (Offsite-box 4205, Folder 4)
    - Financial results: December, 1995-1999 (Offsite-box 4205, Folder 5-6)
- Series III. Advertising Sales Records, 1936-1979; 3.08 Linear feet in 4 record cartons including 18 reels of microfilm, 1 flat box
  The Advertising Sales Records contain records documenting sales and placement of ads, marketing to advertisers, and information on advertisers in Life.
  Organized into three subseries:
  Subseries III.A. General Files
  Subseries III.B. Advertising Sales and Marketing: Paul Hadhazy Files
  Subseries III.C. Advertiser Record Cards
  - Subseries III.A. General Files, 1973; 0.58 Linear feet in 1 flat box
    The General Files contains records on a presentation used to sell advertising for a special edition of Life called Life Beach Party.
    Records remain in original order.
    - Life Beach Party, 1973 (Offsite-box 2005, Folder 8-10)
      Advertising Sales series includes three folders with presentation boards used for selling ads for a special edition of Life called Life Beach Party. One of the folders contains a report which acts as a supplement to the presentation. Since the presentation focuses on ad sales, it appears like the materials would have originated from the advertising sales department. The materials themselves do not indicate the department that produced them.
  - Subseries III.B. Advertising Sales and Marketing: Paul Hadhazy Files, 1955-1979; 2.25 Linear feet in 2 record cartons, 1 flat box
    The majority of these records were binders of rate cards identified as belonging to Paul Hadhazy. The remainder were loose materials found with the binders. The Policy binder contains guidelines and descriptions of the marketing services operations, space renewal credit program, discount structures, tie-in program, and standby space.
    Organized alphabetically.
    - General, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 1)
    - Ad Billing Proposal: Comparison Summary, 1970 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 2)
    - Advertising Forecast Reports, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 3-9)
    - Advertising Procedure Manual, 1967 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 10)
    - Fast Close Ads, 1955-1965 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 11)
    - List of Advertisers, 1969 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 12)
    - The Making of LIFE, 1963 (Offsite-box 3325, Folder 4)
    - PIB Report for 1973, 1972 (Offsite-box 3325, Folder 5)
    - Policy, 1968-1971 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 13)
    - Rate Cards, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 14)
    - Rate Card Binders, 1965 (Offsite-box 3318, Folder 15)
    - Rate Card Binders, 1965-1971 (Offsite-box 3319, Folder 1-8)
    - Regional Computer Input Forms, circa 1970 (Offsite-box 3319, Folder 9)
    - Special Units, 1963-1979 (Offsite-box 3319, Folder 10)
    - Special Unit Rates, 1968-1970 (Offsite-box 3319, Folder 11)
    - Binder Covers, circa 1968 (Offsite-box 3319, Folder 12-13)
  - Subseries III.C. Advertiser Record Cards, 1936-1972; 0.25 Linear feet on 18 reels of microfilm
    The Life Advertiser Record Cards are on microfilm. The dates refer to the original material and not the creation of the microfilm. The domestic advertisers are on fourteen reels and list ads from the original American edition. The international advertisers are on four reels and list ads from international editions. Each record card contains the date of issue for the advertisement, size of ad, if it is in black-and-white or color, and the cost.
    The microfilm is grouped by domestic and international. Within each group, organized alphabetically by name of company or organization placing ad, not the name of the product.
    - Domestic Advertisers, 1936-1972 (Offsite-box 3324)
    - International Advertisers, 1946-1970 (Offsite-box 3324)
- Series IV. Market Research Department Files, 1938-1970; 5.275 Linear feet in 6 record cartons, 1 flat box
  Historical Note
  Based on department heads lists, the Market Research was a department within advertising promotion and circulation from 1949 to 1953. In 1954, these two separate departments were consolidated into one Market Research department but this department disappears from the department heads lists in 1964. Since much of the work done by Market Research overlapped with the work done in the Circulation department, it is believed that Circulation absorbed Market Research. Market Research and Circulation also tended to work conjointly on research projects.
  The Market Research Department Files include materials from 1946 to 1970 and focus on researching circulation statistics. Included in this series are reports on direct mail coverage, reader survey results, sales statements, notes, list of places with special newsstand introduction offers, distribution formula test instructions, store surveys, wholesale estimates, lists of sale sites, newsstand schedules, reports on sales developments, reports on turnover experiment results, reports on sales, reports on newsstand buyers of life, reports on direct sales, stockholder studies, reports on the attitude toward Life, reports on attitudes to proposed time/life record library, reports on subscriber attitudes, study of readership among college students, subscriber surveys, reports on subscriber characteristics, statistics sheets, contracts, clippings, and correspondence. The correspondence in this series discusses newsstand buyers, life readership, newsstand buyer characteristics, formula tests, delivery schedules, issue test sites, posters used at test sites, sales developments, the importance of small dealers in sales, analysis of subscribers, and saturation tests.
  - Attitudes to a Proposed Time/Life Record Library, 1964 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 1)
  - Attitudes to a Proposed Time/Life Record Library: Appendix, 1963 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 2)
  - Babette Kass, 1962-1964 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 3)
  - Babette Kass: Cover Quality Associated with Newsstand Sales, undated (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 4)
  - Census Match, undated (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 5)
  - Jello Radio and TV Promotion: 1964: Newsstand and LCC Sales Data and Renewal, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 6-7)
  - Life Census Matching: 1950 vs, 1960, 1952, 1960-1962, undated (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 8)
  - Life: Cover Renewal Test, 1970 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 9)
  - Life: Cover Survey: 1970: Louis Harris (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 10)
  - Life: Cover Test: 1965 and Earlier, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 11)
  - Life: Cover Test Presentation, undated (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 12)
  - Life: Cover Test Renewal Performance, 1970 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 13)
  - Life: Gift Subscriptions at Christmas, 1964 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: Giftee Test, 1962 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 16)
  - Life: Harris Supplement Survey, undated (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 17)
  - Life: Influence of List and Price on Demo Profile, 1967 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 18)
  - Life: Market Research Reports: Premium Book Offers, 1964 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 19)
  - Life: Miscellaneous Old Studies, 1952-1962 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 20)
  - Life: New York Edition Presentation, undated (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 21)
  - Life: New York Supplement: Roper, 1963 (Offsite-box 3030, Folder 22)
  - Life: Newsstand Buyers Study, 1949-1952 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 1)
  - Life: Newsstand Cover Flap Testing, 1960 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 2)
  - Life: Newsstand Cover Testing: Billing vs. No Billing, 1962 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 3)
  - Life: Newsstand Dateline Program, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 4)
  - Life: Newsstand Price Test, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 5-7)
  - Life: Non-agent Test: Life Lab Test, 1967-1970 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 8)
  - Life: Off Sale Issue Test, 1965 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 9)
  - Life: Penetration: 1964, undated (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 10)
  - Life: Promotion Effect on Mailing, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 11)
  - Life: Promotion Test: 1954 and 1959, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 12)
  - Life: Reader Interest: Mineola Study, 1963 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 13)
  - Life: Reader Interest Survey: Thermometer, 1970 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: Renewal Mailings: Percentage Return by Letter, 1964 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 16)
  - Life: Renewal Survey: H. Kay, 1964 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 17)
  - Life: Response Patterns for Renewal Letters, 1963 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 18)
  - Life: Society Renewal Tests, 1962 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 19)
  - Life: Source Analysis, 1967-1968 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 20)
  - Life: Special Surveys: Price, Newspapers, Sweeps, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 21-22)
  - Life: Subscriber Survey, 1966 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 23)
  - Life: Subscribers and Covers: Babette Kass, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 24)
  - Life: Subscribers and Its Covers, 1965 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 25-27)
  - Life: Supplement Presentation, 1963 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 28)
  - Life: Supplement Study, 1962-1963 (Offsite-box 3031, Folder 29)
  - Life: Supplement Study, 1963 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 1)
  - Life: Supplement Study: Harris, 1969 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 2)
  - Life: Supplement Tests: Weekly Returns Reports, 1970 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 3)
  - Life: Supplements, 1967-1970, undated (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 4-9)
  - Life: Supplements [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Offsite-box R27)
  - Life: Supplements: Evaluation of Publishing Potential of Supplements to Life, 1970 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 10)
  - Life: Survey to Predict Mail Response, 1960 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 11)
  - Life: Trail Subscriber Letter Survey, 1962, undated (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 12-13)
  - Life: Sweepstakes: Subscriber Survey, undated (Offsite-box 3040, Folder 7)
  - Life-saver Surveys, 1963 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 14)
  - List Selection by Geographic Area: Zip Selection, 1972 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 15)
  - Magnacraft Corporate Test, 1968 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 16-17)
  - McIntyre, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 18)
  - Newsstand: Buyer Characteristics, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 19)
  - Newsstand: Cover Flap Test, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 20)
  - Newsstand: Display Tests, 1953-1956 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 21-22)
  - Newsstand: Experimental City, 1956 (Offsite-box 3032, Folder 23)